A Guide to the Records of the Governor's Office, Executive Mansion, 1989-1994
Library of Virginia
- Series VI: General Subjects, 1990-1992., Extent: 1 box. (Box 10)
  - Americans with Disabilities Act: An Implementation Manual for Design Professionals--Pennsylvania (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Training Program for Commonwealth Managers and Supervisors on Title I of the Americans with Disabilities Act--Pennsylvania (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Governor's meal schedules, July-October 1990 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Ruth Jones birthday party, 1 September 1990 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Governor's meal schedule, 11-17 June 1991 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Lunches packed for travel, 11 July 1991 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Governor's bowling team memorandum, 8 August 1991 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Note about meals, 6 September 1991 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Pendleton Cottage inventory, October 1991 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Governor's meal schedule, 1-7 December 1992 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Recipes (Box 10, Folder 26)